[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The roles of Mildred Ratched and Randle P. McMurphy earned Oscars for the starring actors in this movie.", "correct_answer": "One Flew over the Cuckoos Nest", "incorrect_answers": ["American Beauty", "Amadeus", "Driving Miss Daisy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not one of the most popular names for female cats in the USA?", "correct_answer": "Socks", "incorrect_answers": ["Missy", "Pumpkin", "Tigger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What chemical compound is commonly known as vitamin C?", "correct_answer": "Ascorbic acid", "incorrect_answers": ["Acetylsalicylic acid", "Aminobenzoic acid", "Hyaluronic acid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these white foxes populates the polar zone of the Northern Hemisphere?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["White Fox", "Arctic Fox", "Snow Fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1938, Edward  Kasner wrote a 1  followed by 100 zeros and showed it to his baby nephew.  What the baby said became the name of that written number. What did the kid say?", "correct_answer": "Googol", "incorrect_answers": ["Giggle", "Dada", "Gaga"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Friday the 13th, we see Alice, Bill and Brenda playing a game of Strip Monopoly. Who won the game?", "correct_answer": "Nobody won.", "incorrect_answers": ["Brenda", "Bill", "Alice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many babies does the female wombat give birth to every spring?", "correct_answer": "One", "incorrect_answers": ["Three", "Four", "Two"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first TV sitcom?", "correct_answer": "Mary Kay and Johnny", "incorrect_answers": ["The Goldbergs", "I Love Lucy", "The Dobkins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song from a Top Ten movie is rated Number 2 by the AFI, after the all-time favorite Over the Rainbow?", "correct_answer": "As Time Goes By (Casablanca 1942)", "incorrect_answers": ["Mrs. Robinson (The Graduate 1967)", "Singin in the Rain  (same title, 1952)", "Its Hard Out Here for a Pimp ( Hustle and Flow 2005)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term refers to the animal that is the result of crossbreeding between a male coyote and a female dog?", "correct_answer": "Coydog", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Coypup", "Dogote"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did the hat called ushanka originate?", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["China", "Poland", "Canada"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brown Bear/polar bear hybrids occur naturally in the wild.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]